m3forum.net 2005-12-13

# BMW M3 Forum, Auto Information Exchange for BMW Enthusiasts!

---|---  
  
---  
| 

**M3Forum.com Privacy Policy Statement**

> To protect your privacy, M3Forum network follows the following principles for member privacy and data protection.

**WHY WE OBTAIN INFORMATION**

> We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. Generally this information is requested when you create a new user profile on the site to use specific features available only to registered users.
> 
> The primary reason we obtain this information is to make the site easier for you to use by not having you enter information more than once. We may also periodically use your information to alert you to updated information and other new services from M3Forum.com.
> 
> If you choose not to register or provide personal information, you can still use most of M3Forum.com. But you will not be able to access areas or use features that require registration.  
> 

**REGISTERED USER PROFILES**

> When you register, your information is protected by use of a password which you select. Each person who registers must have a unique email address and user name. Duplicate profiles using the same email address or user name are not permitted. We highly recommend that you select a password which is neither common or known to others. We encourage you to NOT use information such as your Social Security Number, Phone Number or Date of Birth as your password.
> 
> If you are a previous registered user and you have lost or forgotten your password, you may only obtain it by email using our "Forgot Password" feature. Click the link on any login page to request your password be emailed to you. We cannot provide your password by any other means.
> 
> We will provide you with the means to ensure that your personal information is correct and current. You may review and update this information at any time. By following the "my profile" link provided on our system, you may view and edit personal information you have already given us. You may also elect to receive or discontinue receiving any email newsletters we may choose to distribute periodically. Once you register, you won't need to do it again. Wherever you go on M3Forum.com, your information stays with you.

**NOTICE TO PARENTS**

> Parents or guardians: we want to help you guard your children's privacy. We encourage you to talk to your children about safe and responsible use of their Personal Information while using the Internet.

---  
  
* * *  

   BMW [E46 M3's](http://www.m3forum.net/gallery/showgallery.php?cat=2&password=)  
   BMW [E36 M3's  
](http://www.m3forum.net/gallery/showgallery.php?cat=501&password=)   BMW [E30 M3's](http://www.m3forum.net/gallery/showgallery.php?cat=502&password=)  

   **E46 M3** :  [Read Reviews](http://www.m3forum.com/m3forumcgi/reviews/review.pl?Action=view&pid=3) |    
   **E36 M3** :  [Read Reviews](http://www.m3forum.com/m3forumcgi/reviews/review.pl?Action=view&pid=2) |    
   **E30 M3** :  [Read Reviews](http://www.m3forum.com/m3forumcgi/reviews/review.pl?Action=view&pid=1) |    
   **Performance Tires** :  
      [Read and Post Reviews  
](http://www.m3forum.com/m3forumcgi/reviews/review.pl?cid=6)    **Performance Parts** :  
   **Wax & Polish**:  

   Spec your E46 M3: [Vote](http://m3forum.com/m3forumcgi/WWCcontests/WWCcontests.pl?action=entryform&filename=spec&id=E36&type=&language=) | [View](http://m3forum.com/m3forumcgi/WWCcontests/subs3.pl?action=ShowTotals&filename=spec&id=E36&type=&language=)  
   Spec your E46 M3C: [Vote](http://m3forum.com/m3forumcgi/WWCcontests/WWCcontests.pl?action=entryform&filename=cabspec&id=E36&type=&language=) | [View](http://m3forum.com/m3forumcgi/WWCcontests/subs3.pl?action=ShowTotals&filename=cabspec&id=E36&type=&language=)  
   Best M3 ever?: [Vote](http://m3forum.com/m3forumcgi/WWCcontests/WWCcontests.pl?action=entryform&filename=bestm3&id=E36&type=&language=) | [View  
](http://m3forum.com/m3forumcgi/WWCcontests/subs3.pl?action=ShowTotals&filename=bestm3&id=E36&type=&language=)   [Survey Main Page](http://m3forum.com/m3forumcgi/WWCcontests/WWCcontests.pl?action=null&filename=quality&id=E36&type=&language=)  

[  
Please Tell a Friend about M3Forum.com](javascript: recommend2\(\))  
  
We designed this website to share our **"BMW M3 experience"** with other enthusiasts and to provide a **  forum** where we can all come together and share anything BMW and M3 related.

We **do not work for BMW or any other company that provides any BMW related goods or services**.  Any information provided here is from our **personal experience** and/or discussions with other M3 enthusiasts and owners.

**Thanks for visiting and Happy Motoring! _  
_ The M3Forum.com Team**

* * *

### **Personal M3 Hisotry:  
 **  
Took Delivery of 2001 E46 M3 - Imola Red/Black leather interior.  4/9/01 (3/01 production)  
Took Delivery of 2001 E46 M3 - Alpine White/Imola Red leather interior.  6/28/01 (5/01 production)

Check out the driving impressions of the two M3's with two different production dates.  [**Review**](http://www.m3forum.com/m3forumcgi/reviews/review.pl)  |  [**Gallery**](http://www.m3forum.net/gallery/index.php)  |  [**Forum**](http://www.m3forum.net/m3forum/)

* * *

M3Forum.com is in no way sponsored, endorsed or affiliated by or with BMW NA / BMW AG or any of it's subsidiaries or vendors.  BMW and M3 is a registered trademark of BMWAG.

* * *
